Thank you for watching!
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
Good evening.
The morning chimes have sounded, and it's us.
We are Shin Chebishi.
EbiChu for short.
Yay!
Please...
Yes, please.
First of all, I would like to introduce myself one by one.
Okay.
Attendance number 3, Rika Mayama.
Yes, ma'am.
Yes, I'm Ayaka Yasumoto.
Next, attendance number 5, Ayaka Yasumoto.
Yes, attendance number lucky 7, Mirei Hoshino.
Yes, attendance number 11, I am Kaho Kobayashi. Please.
And yes, attendance number 12, this is Nakayamashiko.
Yay!
Today, we will have a net signing session by elder sister members.
It's two power generation.
Yay!
This is, you know, this is one camera for each person, so you're in the picture all the time.
That's right.
Please feel free to leave comments.
I'm looking forward to hearing from you.
I don't know how to make comments, so I'm just now getting around to it.
There are a lot of EBICHU music videos here too.
How do I watch them?
How about comments?
How do I view them?
I'm not used to using electronic devices.
They are not used to it.
They're not used to it.
It's supposed to come up, but it's not coming up because you're looking at it on the Web.
Oh, that's funny.
Are you commenting?
Are you looking at it?
What?
I think everyone is watching.
It says something about some people watching.
Thanks for watching some of them.
It's been a while. Online signing.
Yeah, yeah.
This is the kind of benefit event,
Now, my younger sisters, Seira-chan members..,
I've been working hard to make a live concert.
So, you know, face to face,
It's like an event.
Like an event.
We do it through the Internet.
That's right.
Remote high-five.
What?
Princess, what?
Remote high-five.
Yay.
Thank you, Princess.
Touch the princess.
What was that?
Hime.
Before we all met Hime..,
Our nickname, Hime, has taken root.
I was totally surprised.
I've been saying it a lot out in public.
But I probably didn't say much.
Yesterday's broadcast club,
Yesterday at the Ebitu broadcasting club,
I think what we were talking about was broadcasted.
The members call me Hime, too.
I think it all started with the roadmobile.
That was it.
That was the time of Roadmobile,
Just a nickname from a staff member who has been very helpful in the office.
Nowadays, right?
The manager in the sun.
That's how it all started.That's when it started.
is about the same timing that I started calling her Hime,
I'm called Hime at the roadside, too,
I'm also called Hime at the office.
I can't find a nickname other than Hime.
I'm called Mirei-chan,
Mirei-chan was my nickname. I had nothing else.
I couldn't find anything else,
But when you called me "Hime," I felt it fit too well.
I know.
Hime's throat is getting worse.
Yes, she is.
Everyone is coming. She's glad her throat is better.
She's talking.
Thank you.
I really appreciate your concern.
I'm still not feeling my usual self,
Average?
Really? Yay.
I'm glad.
It's nice to be able to communicate.
It's important.
I'd like to thank my seniors for all the help they gave me.
I'm sorry.
Anyway, I had to stop talking.
I received a lot of guidance from senior members of Boyce's group.
That's important.
That happens sometimes.
I'm glad.
At the franchise event, right?
Yes, that's right.
FC event.
There was a franchise event, wasn't there?
Did anyone come?
February 12th.
The 12th.
Come to the star-spacious children.
Yes, I do.
I'm enjoying the FC event.
This year was pretty good, too,
I've been on the offensive in a way.
There's only one game, right?
That was...
I thought, "Oh, well....
Everyone was a little bit on the offensive.
Yes, that's right.
Breaking Down's "orara orara" style.
It's a bit of an ora ora ora type of thing.
I was wondering if I was paying homage to them.
I didn't.
Really,
We invited Sasaki and others,
Really.
I mean, they said they were going to ask him to be a referee, but I don't know what he would do,
But I don't know what I'm supposed to be judging.
I mean, it's not martial arts at all,
It wasn't martial arts.
I thought it must have been out of my area of expertise.
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
It was like a characterization competition,
I mean, you know,
I thought, "Well, I've been doing this song with EBITCHU for a while.
I thought I could at least dance to it.
Ana and Rico were fighting.
Both of them, you know,
You forgot the choreography.
You should do it.
I forgot the moves.
Do it.
I did it.
It comes out of nowhere.
I told Rico to dance,
Aya looked at Rico.
For about three seconds.
She was doing it right here.
I was doing it.
I really forgot about it, to be honest.
It was difficult.It was difficult.
I told them it was my first FG event,
I came in from seasonal use.
Sure enough, I did.
Of course.
That's the default for fan club events.
That's right.
I was surprised, wasn't I?
It's loose, isn't it?
The fan club event.
It wasn't loose this year, was it?
In the second half, you know,
Usually, it's just a joke,
or maybe a little bit of live performance.
But this year, it was an hour each,
This year, however, we had a live part and a one-hour
live part and a joke part.
and a joke part.
That set list was amazing, wasn't it?
It was amazing.
You were full of energy.
You were so energetic.
You were in your second year.
There was that song that you remember from the past.
You don't have to hide it.
The last song?
The second or third song?
It's a nostalgic song.
The current pollen.
That time,
With Emma,
We were holding hands, and I looked at Emma's face.
Emma's face was like a boiled octopus.
She was so cute.
She was so hot, I couldn't even look at her.
Oh, I see.
That's right. It was hot.
I remember that. Kaho and Riko.
When Kaho and Riko first met.
Osaka's "Lively the Feature" when Kaho and I met for the first time.
I remember a little.
At the college arts and crafts show.
They were so solid, both of them.
We were fighting a lot of nerves.
That's right.
It was a franchise event,
I thought they must have been distracted,
I thought they must have been relaxed.
I loved it.
I know.
I was so busy sneezing at Yuna's tissue.
Oh, I see.
It's so loud.
Loud voice.
I was told to sing loud and clear.
So that's what happened.
Studio rehearsal
We were doing it before the show,
When everyone was mic'd up, there was a mic check.
I had to do a microphone check one by one before the show,
First of all.
I would practice my part and
I would practice a little and adjust my voice
and adjust their voice.
After doing something like "ah" or "ah" or something like that
After you say or do something like that...
That's it,
When we were doing that.
Yuna suddenly
clapping,
When I was checking her..,
She clapped so much.
Everyone was saying how cute she was.
It's true.
No one applauds at the microphone check.
It was cute.
Even though there are many parts.
That's right.
You were able to pull it off, weren't you?
Congratulations on the autograph session.
I love it.I love it.
Congratulations on the signing.
Thank you very much.
Now, you know, the WBC just started.
WBC has just started, so everyone is probably
busy and they are watching both.
Unfortunately, I guess it's a weekday for us.
That's for sure.
We're on a holiday, right?
Sunday?
That's terrible.
Start on a weekday,
Let's do our best every day.
Let's get over it.
It's not that they don't think we watch baseball.
I want to believe that.
The middle of the week is the best time to work hard.
You don't work hard.
That's when everyone is like this.
Voice Shutter.
Today is Thursday.
It's the most difficult day of the week.
It's the day of the week.
I think it's the time to say "Let's do our best.
I want Riko to say "Let's do our best.
Me?
I want you to cheer me up.
It's Thursday.
I know you're going through a lot.
Hang in there.
It's just a matter of whether it's up there or in the middle.
What if it was me?
What if it were me?
Let me see your example.
It's Thursday.
Oh, right.
Thursday, Monday, right?
Yeah.
Wednesday, Sunday.
They forgot Tuesday.
Yeah, stupid.
Thursday.
Oh, there were three days when I didn't see you.
It was during the day.
I missed you so much.
But I'm so happy to see you on Thursday like this.
Shut up.
Let's work hard from me too.
Idol-like.
Cute.
Yes, I'm sure.
It's so-so.
Where's Aya?
Aya.
Fight!
Bangs?
I just saw sunflowers around your face.
Fight!
It's great.
It's a power play.
Even power plays want to be dusty.
Dusty.
The last one is the best, isn't it?
No, no, no.
Before the sunset.
You took one dusting and made it a dusting, right?
Well, is the bath water hot enough?
Are you okay?
Set it to 40 degrees and go to bed.
I'll sleep.
Sleep?
40 degrees?
Seven minutes.
It's still cold.Still cold.
By the way, what degree is it always?
It's 40 degrees.
You don't sleep?
Not sleepy?
But wait.
You mean the temperature of the enemy spirits is 38 degrees Celsius, right?
That's right.
You know, like a very comfortable bath.
But isn't it lukewarm?
It's lukewarm.
It's a bath for enemy spirits, so it's 42 degrees for me.
I'm 42 degrees.
Oh, we're the same.
We're the same.
41 degrees.
I was the highest at 43 degrees.
Well then, everyone take a bath and go to bed.
Let's work hard on Friday.
Let's work hard Friday.
Last but not least, the decoys.
That's right.
Ours.
Our fans'.
Our princess.
She's our princess, Hokuzo.
I want to talk about that, too.
That's right.
I'd like to have some words of appreciation.
Yes, of course.
It's Thursday, right?
That's right.
Friday, right?
It's over tomorrow.
Just hang in there for a day or so.
Spartan?
Spartan is good to be told once in a while.
You're a spartan now.
Don't do it.
No, no, no, no.
No, it's not.
I'm sorry.
I woke you up when I fell asleep.
Let's all work hard together tomorrow.
Let's work hard at getting up early.
And you have to eat.
Maybe I should stop.
Just for a minute,
Don't lose heart.
You might hear a gap in your voice.
I waited a little too long to make an error.
Of course you did.
I thought it was Mer-Pen.
It's a new girl.
New girl.
Shut up.
Princess.
Princess episodes.
Tell me.
What?
The school arts and crafts festival.
Was it a college show?
No, it's not.
It's a fan club event, right?
It's a fan club event.
Fan club event.
At the fan club event,
I only have one hour for the live part,
I wanted to have a chance to meet all of you who always support me,
I wanted to have a chance to meet with all of you who always support me,It's an opportunity for us to meet,
I want to have a lot of fun with you,
I would like to have a lot of live and session with everyone,
Kaho-chan was unusually involved in the stirring,
Kaho-chan was unusually stirring up the crowd.
Kaho-chan is a rarity in that she does not do it.
I, Rico, and Mire-chan do it.
The person who goes up.
Mire-chan did it.
I'm not used to it, so I don't know what to do.
I wondered what I should say.
Kaho-chan was the one who gave me the stunt.
Unidentified Junior High School Student X.
I was allowed to enter.
I was put in charge.
I'll tell you where I put it in,
I put the intro at the beginning,
Cha-cha-cha-cha-cha.
I also put it in before the chorus.
This is the most important part of the song.
Mire-chan's Warriors time.
Before the chorus,
Bipipipipi time.
I was told, "Here comes the princess!
What was the idea, really?
I was really nervous.
I had already decided on this when she told me.
I had already made up my mind and talked about it beforehand,
We talked about what to do.
It was too good, wasn't it?
Yes, it was.
Let's ask him to do it.
Beep, beep, beep, beep, beep.
The princess is here!
Zukkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkk.
When I say "incite," I mean, you know, all the fans,
Like, "Let's go!
You're supposed to call out, "Here we are!
But look at this.
But I really laughed at that.
That was great.
It was great.
I was so surprised. I'm really glad.
After the show, Aya and I all thought it was her.
It was just like her.
She was right in front of me, diagonally in front of me.
In formation.
I turned around and looked behind me.
I couldn't dance facing forward.
I want to see.
I was looking at her face during the first half of the chorus.
It was interesting.
It was a real highlight.
I thought I would go see this again somewhere else.
But then again, everyone wants to prep before they ever see it.
I'd love to prep.
What a great way to see such a stunt.
The fan club is next week.
Next weekend, on the fan club site,
I'm going to show you almost all of the FC event on the fan club site.
So, are you in it?
I hope so.
I hope you're in.
Please, everyone can check.
I don't know, but the calls are going to start coming out soon.
In many places.
It's new.
Someone will definitely say it.
I'm sure.
I'm sure they will.
I'd like to see it.
But that's exactly what I'm going to say.
Today was already a war.
You're all fighters, fans.
Leader.
Leader? May I be appointed?
Squire.
Really? Squire?
That'd be great. Thank you, that's great.That's helpful. I appreciate that.
I'm grateful for the role.
I was thinking of practicing.
I heard that I can see it when I come in now.
Let's practice.
I'm not in.
I'd love to join.
So, is anyone really going to join?
Please come and make a call.
It'll be great if you get in.
It's worth seeing.
I like it a lot if it's not worth seeing.
It's worth seeing even if it's not the only reason.
Of course.
They played songs that are rarely played.
We played the King of Kakei Kai's theme and a lot of other songs that are not played very often.
I wonder if it's in there? I wonder if it's in there.
I wonder.
Looking forward to it.
I didn't feel like it was a big arts festival.
It's a picture brow.
I put a lot of cute parts and stuff.
The big show...
We didn't have much to talk about, did we?
Let's talk about it.
It was last year.
That was fast.
The first day of the school festival was Hyuga's graduation live.
We all cried a lot.
The second day was a new live with a new organization.
It was a really different live performance.
I felt like there was an empty space even though it was 2days there.
Looking back on it now.
For sure. It doesn't feel like a consecutive day.
It doesn't seem like it.
It's just a memory.
That's right.
It's like every year at the big arts and crafts festival.
It's the most spirited show of the year.
I put a lot of things into it.
So when I try to talk about it like this
I can't remember what it was.
I think, "Wait a minute, what was it?
Especially on the second day, I can't remember.
I can't remember.
Expecting.
Too desperate.
It was the same with Aika.
It was the same with Ebitu Pride.
New organization...
You don't remember Ebitu Pride at all, right?
You don't remember, right?
You don't remember.
I get a lot of people who say they want to see that show again.
But I don't remember.
I don't remember what we did and how we did it.
I don't remember.
I was still absorbed in it. I did it, though.
That's right.
It was quite a big arts and crafts festival.
At the New Style Arts and Crafts Festival...
What's it called? A tree?
It's a kind of cannewood that came in.
I mean, they really cherished it.
That's what they did.
There were a couple of staging elements.
We three...
I mean, the three of us are the originals.
The members who have been with us since our major label debut
Each of us sang a solo song.
And Kahoriko sang "Friendship Love Letter".
That was really good.
The old songs...
That's right.
Friendship Love Letter was great, wasn't it?
I'm so happy.
That was a song we wanted to do.
We each thought of a song we wanted to play and sent it in.Think about it and send it to me.
I was told to think of something.
But in the end, we all agreed
We had a discussion about what would be best for the place.
Our opinion and the teacher's opinion.
and the teacher's opinion.
The friendship love letter was too emo.
In the end, Mr. Kobayashi said it was a good idea.
So we decided to give it a try.
It's very affectionate.
It turned out to be a good idea.
But you know, after everyone's solos and units
The last superhero was a bit too much for me.
It was a little too touching for me.
You sang it the day before, right?
Yes, that's one of the reasons
When I saw it again
I almost cried.
I'm glad we did it there.
Yes, it was.
To be honest, I was desperate for the show.
I didn't have any.
But when I look back on it...
I cracked up.
I was doing it... like, this kind of thing.
After that...
We did ten songs.
Forenson Punk.
Chancha Chancha
Chancha Chancha.
I really liked Forenson Punk.
That's for sure.
That's cool.
It's like a band.
I've had the opportunity to play a few times at a big show.
I feel like I want to do it full time.
That's why I feel like I'm missing something.
I feel like I'm missing something.
I don't know...
When I see the finished product
I'm happy with the way it turned out.
That's what I thought at the time of the reboot.
At the time of the reboot...
Just the encores.
That's an extravagant use of space.
That's true.
And then in the second half of the show, we had to carry the band on our backs.
And that's what we wanted to do.
We were able to express our will even more.
The stronger Ebitude
I guess you could say...
We did it, didn't we?
It was divine.
I'm glad.
The band Horaceon Punk
There's a next one.
The band's Hawthorne punk.
And the arrangement.
And the final formation...
It's a little bit different
And the arrangement...
It was...
The band members liked it too much.
In the feedback section
I usually stand vertically
We usually do it vertically.
but when we get together and do it like this
It felt so good to do it like this.
It felt really good.
It was so much fun!
When we played "Go to Osaka"...
Everyone loved it so much.
We were like, "Let's do it again.
The day before.
Isn't that better?
Isn't it more dynamic? That's what I said.
But we can't change it a day before.
It's not good to change it the day before.
It's the best way.
We spent a lot of time on that one, didn't we?You spent a lot of time.
You said you wanted to do it, and I said, "Let's stop.
Wait a minute. Let's try it again.
This is better.
You were doing it.
Like that.
Like before... and before... and before...
This time we're going to have a big show.
The last spring tour.
The 9th one, the same as the spring tour.
Mr. Yusuke...
Mr. Yusuke has been thinking about it.
Every time I work with Yusuke
I'm learning Yusuke's ideas.
it's like I'm learning Yusuke-ism.
Yes, that's right.
It's nice.
Don't tell me you didn't see it.
Please don't say that.
I haven't seen it.
But, you know, the more I'm involved, the more I'm involved, the more I'm able to do these sessions.
The more I'm involved, the more I'm involved, the more I'm able to have sessions.
You know, the more I'm involved, the more I'm able to have sessions.
So, it's fun to combine our isms, maya maya-ism, and atomato-ism.
I'm having a lot of fun combining these two isms, and I'm having a lot of fun doing it every day.
And the spring tour?
Oh, yeah, is there going to be a spring tour? Spring tour, too.
Yusuke. Always, always.
You'll definitely find out. They'll find out.
What will happen? This will be conveyed.
I guess I'm just looking forward to it. Yes, that's right.
The DVD is, uh, Kijio-sensei, you know. Yes, that's right.
The DVD is edited by Kijio, the director of the show, who has done a lot of work on it. He is full of love.
Yes, yes. And Yusuke-san's, I don't know, many props appear in the production.
I'm looking forward to seeing what will happen when Kijio-sensei's loving drawings are combined.
It will be released on March 29.
Yes. It will include Hinata-san's graduation live performance and a live performance by us new university students, so please enjoy it.
Please enjoy it. Please enjoy it.
So, I'll get right to it... I'm wearing that outfit that I remember.
That's right.
Shall we start writing our signatures?
In this outfit.
I'm writing. It's finally started.
Indeed. But I did get a comment from a commenter saying, "What about autographs? I'm sure we could talk for an hour and a half, couldn't we?
Maybe we can talk for an hour and a half. We could talk for an hour and a half.
Shall I start with Mayuka? I'll go first.
Let's cut to the chase. Let's get down to business.
It's 1-0 already.
Ayaka. From Ayaka.
Ayaka, I've applied for this one.
Mr. Daikibo. Thank you very much for your hard work at GoToOsaka.
I'm glad you cheered for the first time because it was the Corona disaster that made us a family.
I'm looking forward to the first tour.
I love Rika-chan. I love you too, Ayaka. Thank you.
So I will write.
I will write here.
Great.
Then, Ayaka like that will draw next.
Ayaka like that.
Not you?
Who will draw Ayaka?
I wonder.
Meka-chan.
Oh, no.
We get it wrong every time. It's Nuka-chan.
Remember.
I read it differently every time.
I'm Nuka-chan.
I love Aya-chan's smile, so please call me by my name gently.
Nuka-chan.
You're so sweet.
Gentle.
I finally did it.
You're so sweet.
Pull.
Ten.
Tamamin-san. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
A word for the spring tour.
Let's feel the ism.Let's feel the ism.
Let's go.
We are waiting for you.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to going to places I don't know.
So I'm going.
Yuka-chan.
I'm cheering for you from Hokkaido.
I'm looking forward to the tour.
Thank you very much. I'll be waiting for you.
I'll come to Hokkaido.
Please look forward to it.
I went.
Minori.
I'll keep supporting you.
I love you, Riko.
Thank you very much. I'll keep on coming.
Hoyo-san, I'm rooting for you, Maru. You always cheer me up.
Maru, I don't know how you talk like that.
Maru Thank you very much.
Just Maru. It's so Maru. It's nice. Thank you.
I'll take Maru's place.
Compton.
I'm looking forward to seeing you in your new role, Harufer.
I'm looking forward to it. Thank you very much.
I'll go next.
Mr. Arrow, I had the best time with you last year at the World Cup, watching your delivery in the middle of the evening and having fun with you on Twitter,
It made me feel sad. I hope we can have such an event again. Now.
You just came back.
What? I heard you scored a point for Japan.
That's great.
It came back in the comments.
But you know what?
It's interesting that the event changes so much.
The time is just right.
I pulled it.
Yes, Mayu.
Mayu.
Good evening, Kaho.
Good evening.
I was so happy to see Kahoriko's friendship love letter at the big show, which I had always wanted to see.
I'm excited to see many performances by the 10 members of Ebichu on the spring tour.
Keep up the good work, Kaho! Thank you.
Thank you.
Yes, I'm here. Okay, I'm here.
I'm Nana.
I recently got into Ebitu and became a Tatsudo fan. Thank you.
Nice Tatsudo.
I'm a Tatsudo guesser with my dad.
Let's be friends and support each other. Keep up the good work without Tatsudo.
Suko.
Me too, Suko.
Rikosuko.
Thanks.
Nana-chan.
Then I'll play Mayu too.
Yae-chan.
Mayu sings.
I spread my wings over your sleepless heart and my destiny was accelerated.
I love it. Thank you.
I could hear it.
I can hear it.
I heard it.
Yae-chan has to eat without asking.
I'm sorry.
I have to tell myself.
It's too late.
Next, Arisa.
Arisa.
I always look at your instagram to take care of my skin and work hard. Thank you very much.
I'm looking forward to seeing you on the spring tour.
Thank you very much.
By the way, what do you recommend these days?
What do you recommend these days?
You're doing Q10 and other eye candy right now, aren't you?
I'm sure they are.Indeed.
YouTuber Hyuk-kun, who has a cosmetics certification, has a lot of trust in the products he recommends.
I see.
Oil to beat acne.
What should I do with the one he mentioned recently?
I want it.
It's really great.
What?
Didn't you say you wanted it?
I want it.
Like, "I want this next one.
Oil to beat pimples.
You should take a look.
If you look up "acne oil," you'll find it.
I'm sure they'll put "beat up pimples" in there.
I'm sure they'll put it in.
It didn't come up earlier.
I'm going to beat it up.
Please send it to me later.
I'll be next time.
Thank you very much, Aragon.
Milie was cool in the Breaking Down Mouth Pack.
Thank you very much.
I tried to use the voice function at the Breaking Down, but everyone was talking and I couldn't use it at all.
I will try my best.
I know I'm going to lose my timing.
Thank you very much, Atsu-chan.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you for listening.
This year's speaking place was an important story.
I am so glad I got to see it.
I am looking forward to the spring tour.
See you soon.
Glad you could make it. Thanks for coming to Important Stories.
It was really interesting.
I was so nervous. I was so nervous.
I tried my best.
There were a lot of people who laughed.
That's true, but...
Comedy.
Why, because it's a comedy.
But I was really happy.
Continue.
Thank you, Tsukai-san.
It didn't say anything?
It said none.
So there were some people who had.
Easy.
I ain't got nothing more to say to you.
You didn't say.
No, I'm sure it's nothing.
Someone else had it.
Missy atmark Maya Maria.
Ms. Mayamalika, I'm always rooting for you.
Keep up the good work!
I'll do my best.
You're giving blood and flesh. Yes, I have in the past. Thank you for your blood donation.
Next, Yume-chan, I'm looking forward to the spring tour of Ebichu.
What's that TikTok video you were taking recently?
You were filming the feeling of love, the feeling of love, and we were all filming on TikTok.
That's true. Maybe it was just a moment.
It's going fast, isn't it? Even if it's tonight.
Yeah, I'm really fast myself.
Let's go!
I pulled a cat.
From upstairs...
Shino-san.
You've been a great help to me. Thank you for always being so sweet.
What? Huh?
I'll save you.
Uh...
Princess.
Thank you, princess.
You mean "thank you" instead of "you're cute.
Thank you for saying I'm pretty is probably the nicest thing I've ever heard.
That's great. That's great.
She's gonna be popular. She's gonna be popular.
So popular. So popular.
Yes, Penrabunbun, we had a lot of fun on stage.
Thank you. Thank you.Thank you. Thank you.
That's great. Thank you, Penrabunbun.
So that's it.
Yes, I'll be there.
Reina, Riko, you look lovely today. I'm looking forward to the spring tour. Thank you.
I wonder if you imagined she's cute today.
You think she's cute every day.
You're absolutely adorable. Aren't you?
Reina-chan.
In the meantime, I've quietly pulled it off.
Seto.
I'm always encouraged by your lovely singing voice and cute cheerful smile.
Take care of yourself and don't overdo it, and I'll support you no matter what.
Oh, I'll always support you no matter what!
Thank you very much.
You take it easy too, Seto. Thank you.
Thank you.
Maya's Samselling
Samselling.
What happened?
Next, Konami
Thank you for always making me so happy!
Thanks to Aya-chan, I'm happy every day!
Aya-chan, please give me one word that makes me squeamish.
Aya-chan, please give me one word that makes me happy.
Bleep, beep, beep.
It's not coming.
Can you come?
Go home.
She's not coming.
She's not the princess.
We got a live one.
I'm in the middle of this.
I'll go next time.
Ojipen.
I love Siri TV's leading man. Looking forward to the spring tour.
So polite.
Where are you coming? I'll be waiting for you.
Thanks.
Thanks a lot.
Okay, next, Yume. I always support you. Ebitu is the best and the strongest now that we have 10 members.
Question. What are you most into now?
Sign-writing.
In front of everyone's face group.
That's what they say.
I wonder what they are into.
Hitomi. Thank you very much.
You cried again.
I wonder if Riko's fans really like Miko.
I wonder if they are shy.
I forgot to write that.
It's funny.
I don't need to put it into words. I'm sure.
You and Riko are the type of people who say "yes".
I pulled it out.
Shiru-chan. Hello. I went to the dialogue with the Staff Lances Leaders. It was a lot of fun. I will participate in the spring tour in Osaka. I am looking forward to it. I love you, Mayama-san.
You wrote this with a lot of surprise marks. Thank you very much.
Next, Honoka-chan. I always support you. Seeing EBICHO really gives me strength.
I really love the 10 of you who enjoy being idols with all your heart. I will continue to support you. Thank you very much.
I am so happy.
I'll go next time.
Ayako. I am looking forward to the spring tour with the new organization. I will continue to support you.
Where will you come? Please come to see me. I'll be waiting for you.
Thank you very much.
no tommy. Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
When I am lost, I think about what I would do if I were a shrimp.
www ebcd
What? How do you read it?
It's a grass, isn't it? Laugh?
Laugh?
Quick, grass.
The grass is fast.
Is that what I think it is?
Grass. You mean grass.
Laughing Shrimp D.
What do you mean?
I want to see, I want to see, I want to see.I want to see it, I want to see it, I want to see it.
If you can see it.
Laughing Laughing Shrimp C.
Laughing Laughing?
I'm laughing so hard I'm getting excited.
Laughing shrimp C.
Laughing Shrimp C. Don't you love it?
Yes, I do.
I love EbiC.
Isn't this so good? Use this or use it.
Use it or use it.
I love EbiC.
I'm embarrassed to read "WW" for "lol".
I'm embarrassed to read "WW".
I'm so embarrassed now.
You're my best uncle.
Thank you.
Now they know who I am.
I've revealed my uncle side.
I'll go now.
Thank you, Koro.
Dear Riko.
If you're reading this, it means I've won.
I'm screaming like a beast right now. Please work with me in acting in the future.
So you're an actor?
You want to be an actor?
What about the part of the beast?
What role should I play? The Beast?
The Beast, the Beauty and the Yajilin?
I'll play a beauty.
Then Yazilt?
Where do they talk about the beast Cheikh? He is.
As a beauty.
Stop howling.
The beast and the kimono together, you see.
I'm here at last.
Haruka.
None.
There is no such thing.
There's a part of me that's waiting a bit.
Indeed.
We're really lucky to be able to enjoy everything, aren't we?
I've laughed so much today that I'm thirsty.
That's right.
I'm more tired than during the show.
We talked too much.
Go on.
Hmm? What?
Jinryanju-san.
Okay, I almost misread that.
Thank you Aya for everything! Your performances, daily posts and work inspire me!
I love the recent vintage clothing boom! I will continue to support you! I love you! Thank you!
Secondhand clothes
Old clothes
I'll go then. Mr. Takeyon
I will always support Mirei, who is getting more and more beautiful these days.
Thank you.
I'm glad.
And Maki-san
I always get power from Kaho's smile. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
She says she's getting power from you.
I'm glad.
I'm going.
Yes, ma'am.
Momochan.
Thank you very much.
Why so much?
Do you think it's because...
You know, your crush...
didn't you comment on it?
I'm sorry if I made a comment.
I'm sorry.
Thirteen...
I can't take it anymore.
I'm not even halfway through.
I'm laughing too hard.
I heard that.I heard about it.
Oniichi.
Are there any sacred places of anime you would like to visit in the future?
The answer was "yes.
Holy Land
I'm not the type of person who goes on pilgrimages to holy places.
I'm not the type of otaku who goes on pilgrimages to holy places.
I see.
But you're right.
I've always been...
There's an anime about skating called "Llewion Ice.
There's an anime about skating, and I've been waiting for a sequel to it.
If they said there would be a sequel, I'd be waiting for it all the time,
I'd like to go to the holy place of "Llewelyn Ice".
Where?
The holy place for "Llewion Ice" is there, Karatu? Karatu?
Karatu?
A place called Karatu.
Wow.
I want to go there.
I see.
Yes, I do.
Next, Carrie.
Dear Aya, thank you for your always wonderful performance.
I can feel your texture,
Texture?
I love your textured voice.
I'm glad to hear your songs on TikTok and other media these days.
I love the fact that you exist in the first place.
Please listen to the song.
I have something to say. Aya is cute after all.
I love you, I love you, I love you.
I finally found my princess.
The reason I was born was to meet Ayaka.
Let's walk through life together.
I love you more than anything in the world.
I love you.
Thank you very much.
That's great.
A real love factory.
That's great. Thank you very much.
I think this is the first time I got the Gachikoi Factory. Probably.
Ayaka's one has a lot of nuclear fission, right?
So many.
I'm surprised.
Emotions I don't have.
I guess fans have different personalities.
I think Riko's item was probably given to my guy.
I see you have an extra one.
Thank you.
I'll go next time.
You look like a mama-mama.
I love the new B team. I will keep supporting them.
Thank you very much.
It's pretty simple for my fans.
Simple.
But they are very complimentary.
That's for sure.
Thank you. Please give me more compliments.
Thank you, Tama.
I will go to Harutsu Sendai, Morioka, and Niigata.
I hope to shoot in Yokohama, too.
Good luck. I'll be waiting for you. Let's have fun.
Thank you very much.
I'll follow you.
Ms. Karine.
I love your cute little girl, and I love your beautiful big sister, too.
Thank you very much.
Congratulations.
It's wonderful. I got a comment.
Mayama, I will always support you, Masa-san.
Thank you very much.
Please keep supporting us. Please keep up the good work.
I wondered what kind of chokes I would get.
I'm under a lot of pressure.
I'm so happy because this is the first time I've seen your chalk, Dojimbo.
Thank you very much.
A little bit between the lines plenty.Plenty of space between the lines.
Plenty of space between lines.
Open type?
Hmm? Lots of space between lines?
Lots of space between lines?
Open type?
Neither.
Thank you, Mika.
I love the University of Arts costume, the colors are lovely, and the shape is great, one of my favorite costumes.
I am glad to have it with me as a checkerboard.
What is your favorite costume?
Is it your favorite costume?
Favorite costume so far?
I liked this outfit a lot.
It's cute.
The cute Bastel outfit.
What's your favorite?
The best.
I liked Karma's outfit.
Karma is cute too.
Is it?
The first one in the first part.
Kana?
Yes, and Ishi-chan.
Po-chan's presence always encourages me. Thank you very much.
Okami style.
Thank you very much.
It is Okaho, Okami style.
Please take your time.
This vest with the black color.
It's a little bit like a ryokan hostess.
I was filming on TikTok a while ago, and you can just see this part of the vest.
Okami?
Only one lady?
Thank you for coming all the way from far away.
Thank you very much for your hospitality today.
Please make yourself at home. I have an open-air brass.
Please take your time.
It's a nice inn.
It's a nice place.
I'll be going.
Chika-san.
I love private art studies.
I will continue to support you.
Thank you very much.
Next, let's go to Ms. Non-chan.
I have been swamped in the swamp of Mayama since I saw her up close for the first time at Samyen.
I want to go to Maya Mania next time. I will continue to love it.
The level 7 video of Maya Mania is now available.
Uchi ya Asuke, please watch it.
More and more,
More beautiful.
Please drown in the swamp.
I beg you.
It was so beautiful.
Swampy.
It was great, wasn't it?
You were so good.
It was beautiful.
Thank you.
You're beautiful.
I'm beautiful.
Wow.
Next!
Next, Ayaka!
You're the most unbelievable.
Next, Kanata.
My favorite guess. Aya-chan with her aura and physical sparkle. Love you forever and ever! Thank you!
Okay, next, Asuna-chan, thank you very much.
Good evening, it's getting warmer, how are you feeling? I'm very happy to hear that Iray-chan and others are healing well.
Yay!
I've been playing Molek for work and I know most of the rules.
Oh, yeah, I'll format it and hold a moruku tournament for FC members only
Hime, Hime and I suddenly started playing Mork, and I was so surprised We had so much fun, and it was a cotword?
What? It's so much fun, let's all do it together. What was that? What's the score? 50 points.
There are some rules, but it's pretty easy.
You'll have to teach us. We'll have to learn.
Take care and good luck with your work, Asra.We wish you good luck with your work and good luck with Asra's work.
Thank you very much for your smile and singing voice with negative ion effect.
Thank you very much. I would like to see Po-chan's twin-tail and ponytail at the live performance.
I will continue to support you, Po-chan and Evitin!
Maybe we'll do it someday.
Maybe someday.
What about twin tails?
I've never seen twin tiles.
Twin tiles. You know, that.
I don't do that.
We've only done it once, right?
We did it once at Idol Fest.
Wasn't there a time when we all did Mini's hair?
Oh, that was a while ago.
That was a long time ago.
At the Family Live at the Maihama Amphitheater.
That time you had your hair in a bun downstairs, right?
Because it's so close to Maihama.
Maihama's character Mickey.
That's right, that's right.
We did hair and stuff.
I'll go on to the next one.
Keisuke
I won a ticket for the spring tour!
It's been a while since I've performed live.
Bittin! I'm really looking forward to calling out "I'm in love with you! I'm really looking forward to calling out "I'm in love with you!
Please take care of yourself and do your best!
I'll be rooting for you.
Thank you.
Next, Kei-san.
Thank you for everything. Rika-chan and I have become a 10-member group, and now I and I have become a 10-member group, and I love the powered-up Ebichu.
I am looking forward to seeing your cool singing voice and dancing in the spring tour, and I will devote myself to my work every day.
I love to read, so I'm looking forward to reading the blogs of the older sister members.
Hey, hey, hey.
Did you hear something?
Can't you write? I will.
I heard that you like to read,
You should check out the many books on EBITCHU.
Kao-chan, last time I saw you, you were writing in Idol & Lead.
Yes, on March 28th? It's coming out.
That's right.
If you look up the EBITCHU mark, you will find it.
Sometimes I buy the document when it's napper-in. Read it.
Next, Maru-chan.
Aya-chan's singing voice, performance, and passion for EBITCHU always inspire me.
I'm really happy to be able to promote Aya-chan. I will continue to follow you.
I love Aya and EBITCHU. Thank you very much.
I love you!
Ebi!
I'll go next time.
Thank you, Yosan.
I always look forward to your insta and TikTok posts.
I hope your throat is getting better.
I'm looking forward to hearing your singing voice and performance after your revival in the spring tour.
Well, I'll do my best.
Let's do our best.
I'll do my best to fix it. Thank you.
Next, let's go to Miyama-chan.
Mommy, Mommy, Mommy.
Mamiyama-chan, you were here earlier, too.
I love you, Mamiyama-chan, and I love the new Mi-chu. I will continue to support you.
Thank you very much.
Let's see, here we go.
Chi-chan, Rittan, Kokotan, I love you.
When I call you two, Rikokokoko, kokokoriko, oh.
Rikokoriko, Rikokoriko, Rikokoriko, Rikokoriko, Rikokoriko, Rikokoriko...
I call you Kokoriko.
Oh, I see.
It sounds good.
I'll be here.
Thank you very much.
Two uncles are coming.
Nice uncles.
Uncles will come, won't they?
Next, I'm going to go.
Ayumi.
I love you, always cheerful Mayama-chan. Thank you, I love you.
I had my first sakatsu experience.
It was very refreshing and I want to continue to push forward. So ,I am very refreshed and want to continue to push forward. So ,
Let's keep sakatu together.
Best sauna day ever.
Next, Kan-san.
I was really impressed to see the 12-year buchi at the big show.
I thought I could love everyone more and more,
I love you even more now.
Please keep up the good work. I love you the most in the world.
Thank you very much.
Hatsusho in Management
Hatsusho of Management
Since Mae-chan became the Corona disaster, I've only been able to go to the live shows in Kyushu.
But the two-shots we've been taking and talking online and the social networking updates you've been giving me have made me feel closer to you and have been a great source of emotional support.
I'm going to see you more this year and I can't wait to talk to you in person.
I love you so much. Thank you so much.
Please come to see me, I'll be waiting for you.
And Momoka-chan.
Hello, Po-chan.
I like Wolf Po-chan so much that I had my hair cut last year.
I've already cut it off.
Po-chan, you look great with any kind of hair style.
Is there any other hairstyle you would like to try?
What other hairstyle would you like to try?
Nagi-chan's hair in Nagi no Ooitama.
A loose afro.
I want to try a loose afro.
It's cute, isn't it?
It's cute. I want her to do it. It looks good on you.
I want to do that.
Then I'll go.
Yasusan.
Thank you for always cheering me up.
Thank you, too.
It's nice.
Last then.
Last one.
Last one in this outfit.
Let's go.
The last one chosen.
This is the guy.
Mio-chan.
Good evening, Mr. Mayama.
I always get full of energy from you.
I was able to hear you sing live for the first time at last year's spring tour, and I was really impressed by your singing.
I'm looking forward to seeing you again this year. Thanks a lot, Mio!
The winner was Mio!
The last one is this kete!
Akane-chan I'm so happy to be able to see the sparkling Aya-chan in real time.
I want to continue to see various Aya-chan in the future I will always love you.
Last but not least, Lucas, I'm looking forward to your spring tour.
Thank you very much. I'll be waiting for you. Please come.
Last but not least, this is Miyu.
Thank you for always cheering me up.
Po-chan, you're becoming more and more like a big sister. I'm a big fan of your hair, especially when it's curly.
She's so beautiful, it brings tears to my eyes. I'm looking forward to seeing her in live performances, and I'll continue to support her with my charm.
I love dumplings, too. I love dumplings, too.
Last but not least, this is Chiaki.
Good evening, Riko. Thank you for bringing us together. I love the costumes from the school arts and crafts festival, so I'm glad to be your checkered guest.
I'm looking forward to meeting all the members of Ebichu and getting a lot of sparkles in the spring tour. Thank you very much.
Cheki-chan.
I like it. It looks like the last one.
It doesn't say anything.
It's the last one.
That's interesting, though.
It's interesting, but...
Thank you very much.
I'll take the checks for the costumes here, yes. Thank you very much.
Even if you didn't win, I will continue to sign and write with love.
Please wait for them. It will be delivered to your home.
So, next up........
Yes, I think it's a good idea to continue, but right now I'm having my hair replaced in a temporary way, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea.
But when I talk to her, she says it's okay, that it's not mixed up.
I'm sure it'll be fine. Thank you very much.
Next is the new clothes version.
You know...
I'm sure there are some of you out there whose hearts are racing.
I'm sure there are.
It's our turn.
Tell them.
"I'll be waiting for you.I'll wait for you.
Then I'll start!
I'll start with Mayama
Here I go!
What's up
Here they come
From you just a little while ago
There are so many ways to go!
Good evening, I'm cheering for Maya from Hokuriku.
I hope you will come to Hokuriku again!
I'll continue to support you from here on out with my charm.
I look forward to your continued support.
That's right.
I'm glad to hear that. But I love it!
There are many delicious foods and hot springs.
I've been to Niigata too.
I'm going to the campaign next week, it's been announced, and I'll be broadcasting live on satellite.
Please listen to the live satellite broadcast.
Then... I see Maboroshi. Maboroshi?
Yes, Maki, Maki, I love you, Aya. I'm looking forward to the spring tour.
Wait for me.
She's the one we've been waiting for.
Maki
Maki!
Down from here
Here we go.
Here I go!
Oh no. Let's play it again.
What?
I played the pear and the really long one.
Oh, I played both.
Then! Here we go!
Let's try again.
Miku and Mirei-chan, you are the cutest in the world.
Thank you.
I have a question for the cutest princess in the world.
Is there anything you would like to do or eat if you go to Okinawa for your spring tour?
I'm going to Okinawa too, so I'd like to know your recommendation.
Well, if it's already in Okinawa,
I love umi budou (sea grapes) so much,
I recommend buying two packs of umi budou to take home.
I would eat a lot of them.
Also, I want to eat aoki saba (mackerel),
I want to eat mozuku tempura,
I also want to eat mozuku vinegar.
There are so many.
Please eat them.
Mozuku is delicious.
I like it a lot.
Yes, and Satoshi-san. Let's go to SSA for sure. I'll be rooting for you all the way. Thank you very much.
I'm glad. I'll follow you.
Oh, well...
Thank you, Riri.
Nothing special.
Here they come. Yui.
Maya's words always save me.
I will try my best to become a wonderful adult woman like Maya-san someday.
I have always and will always love you, Maya. I'm glad, Yui.
I hope you won't become like me, though.
That's fine.
I will continue to do my best so that I can be your target. Thank you.
Yes, followed by Mr. Saint.
I am always cheered up by Ebiju's smile.
I will continue to support you with all my strength. Thank you very much.
Wait, wait, wait. I'll go next time.
I'm glad I can buy Yune-chan's cheki. You always cheer me up. Thank you.
Thank you, Mayu. I'll cheer you up.
Here you go.
I flew here.
Thank you. Hime.
No...
The last one is light.
Continue,
Hime.
Mr. Nonnon.
How are you, Po?
I am fine.
I am going on my first spring tour under the new organization.
It's a little complicated, but I'm looking forward to it.
Please take care of yourself.
Please take care of yourself too, Nannan-san.Please be careful, Nanan-san.
Yes, thank you. I'll be on my way.
Dear Mr. Kuro and Riko. I have been supporting you since high school.
Before I knew it, three years have passed since I started working. I am surprised.
Every time I see your success, I will do my best.
Please continue to cheer up our family, the engine man of Ebitune.
Thank you very much. Mr. Kuro.
Well, let's continue,
What's it called? Monin-chan?
Oh, it's a little difficult. It means "moe, moe, moe, moe, moe." It means "robe.
It's called moe-chan. There are people called Moe-chan, right?
Moe-chan, moe-chan, moe-chan, moe-chan, moe-chan?
Mocchan, mocchan, mocchan, mocchan, mocchan.
Well, I had a lot of fun and laughed a lot at the FC Ibee the other day, and the second half of the event was a lot of fun.
I'm looking forward to seeing the 10 Ebitu-chan and I want to follow them all the way.
I love Mayama san's songs, so I hope I can listen to them for a long, long time.
I love Mayama-san's Ebichu. Please keep up the good work, Ebitu-chan.
Who? Who?
How do you read?
Mo-chan.
Thank you, Mo-chan. Come to SSA for sure.
Next, Hana-chan. Thank you so much for the online award meeting.
I love your bumbling, clumsy and sweet personality. Thank you very much.
I'm trying my best to take care of my skin by referring to Aya-chan's skin care tips.
Also, I got a job offer at a local hotel, so congratulations! Congratulations on a job well done!
That's great!
That's great! I hope Aya-chan will send her power to my hometown, Springai.
Wow!
Is that the highest point in Hokkaido?
It's up there.
I hope you'll do the live concert in Yushinai, too.
I'm planning to go to Hokkaido for the spring tour. Thank you very much.
Here it comes!
Yutaka, nothing special. He's here, he's here, he's happy.
Yes, and Rina-chan, Po-chan Po-chan Po-chan!
Wow! Yes! Nothing special!
Po-chan, Po-chan, here I come! Did you call me?
Yes!
Mai, I will continue to support you. I love you. Thank you for your smiles and energy.
Thank you, too.
Here I go. Ta-da!
Oh, I can't read again. Oh, you wrote it. Thank you, Natsuka. Natsuka.
I'll read it as Natsuka, so you wrote it.
I'll read it as Natsuka. Thank you, Natsuka.
I love your personal clothes.
Do you have a specific brand in mind?
I would like to know if it's in stores or online. It's the season of spring clothes.
Today, we're going to wear, well, personal style outfits, or rather, costumes.
I'm wearing a brand that I often wear in my casual wear, and I'm wearing it today.
It's called Dontokyo.
It's cute.
It's a little bit cute. It's cute.
It's cute, and that's why I feel that way, but it's a very fashionable brand, and I'd like you to wear it,
I've been buying a lot on ZOZOTOWN lately.
Hee.
I heard they are doing it because of the "spring" season.
They are doing it because of spring.
New on Saturday.
I bought a primary color bag at ZOZOTOWN.
I have to buy it.
But I've been wearing a lot of white lately.
Ha.
Please refer to it.
Next, here he is. Mr. Andrew.
Eggplant.
He's here.
Eggplant?
Eggplant.
Did you say eggplant? Eggplant.
So they announced the extras for the music video.
Oh, they announced it already?
I won an extra. That's true, everyone suddenly did.
I'm looking forward to working with you on the shoot.
Are extras supposed to be auditioned for acting?
Is there? Is there?
Aya, is there an actor like a female director?
I'm not an actor.
He said, "Here's what I'm going to do.
I'll be there.
Shota and Mirei, your smiles always cheer me up.Shota and Mirei, your smiles always cheer me up.
Thank you for everything. Please continue to support me a lot.
Please give me lots of support.
Smile!
Bye bye!
I'm still watching. I'll be watching till the end.
The high view is amazing.
I can't get enough of this tactic.
It's a tactic.
They push you away.
I'm not scared.
I'll pick a picture of you smiling.
I'm scared.
Next, Tokiku.
Po-chan love.
Love, love, love.
Love Po-chan. Love, Po-chan. Thank you. Thank you simply. Love.
I'll keep going. Positive Leo. Thank you very much. Hello, Naka Yamashiko. I would like to announce my favorite part of Naka Yamashiko.
I love her singing voice dada. I love her majestic behavior on stage. I love her words, which may be few in number, but they convey her feelings clearly.
I love his sharp criticism of the recent members.
I love that you are clear about what you like and what you are not interested in.
I love that they are polite about what they like.
I also love that he has a cute face.
So I love you. Thank you.
Thank you.
You are overflowing with love.
From the inside to the outside.
It's all Mr. Ukka.
I drew Mr. Ukka.
Thank you very much. Thanks for your hard work, Ebichu.
My goal last year was to strengthen my core, but it didn't work at all.
So I wonder if you could give me a shout out so that I can do my best this year. Thank you very much.
You can't train your core in a day, so please work on it every day.
The best way to strengthen your core is to breathe.
Breathe in, breathe out!
That's great.
You are a trainer.
You've recently started Pilates. Pilates is great. It is.
It's great. Next, Akio Takatsuka.
I love your cheerfulness, Yasumoto-san. Thank you very much.
You were cheerful. I was really cheerful now.
I was afraid. I was afraid.
I was kind of wandering. I was wandering around as a man.
Yasumoto-san's cheerfulness, I was thinking deeply.
You're falling for a moment, don't fall.
Stop it, really.
Thank you very much.
I'll go.
Next?
Yes, next.
Shuichi Iwae-mon no Shuichi.
Shuichi Iwaiemon no Shuichi.
Well, I guess that's okay. Iwasan.
Miru-chan's smile is so cute.
I'm always cheered up by her smile. I'm really looking forward to the spring tour.
I'll be waiting for you in Niigata. Please wait for me.
I will continue to support Mirei-chan with all my strength.
Thank you very much. How long will there be snow in Niigata?
I would like to ask.
It seems like you are not coming back.
You will be there next week, right?
I will be there next week. I wonder if there will be snow or not.
I just heard that Hokuriku is not Niigata.
It said something like Hokuriku is not Niigata.
Hokuriku is not Niigata in Hokuriku.
Hokuriku region?
Hokuriku, right? Niigata.
It was written.
Is the commenter wrong?
I heard it's in there.
I lost track. Chile.
Are you in?
Which way?
What do you think?
But the Hokuriku Campaign is in there a lot, isn't it?
The Hokuriku Campaign is in there, isn't it?
I'm not going.
How about the mountains?
Tube?
Tube? He says it's not the Hokuriku area. He's doing a lot of ronso. It's a long way up. Tube?Tube? It's not a national land, he said. It's pretty ronso. It's a tube. Tube.
Is that it? Is that the way to put it? Is it something like...? Like Niigata and Fukui. I heard Niigata is a tube.
It's a tube. Why is Hokuriku always in the Hokuriku Campaign? It's true, the Hokuriku Campaign is always in Niigata.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors to decide. This is Hokuriku and this is the Tube region.
Oku-gu, rock-paper-scissors-scissors! Oh, the Tube region won.
That's very Tube-like. It's that easy to decide.
I can come up with anything I want.
Now that we have decided on the Tube Region, let's move on.
Nabe-san.
Your singing voice always gives me courage to the point of tears. I was also impressed by your white gentleman's performance in the Queen's Tale.
The tour is about to start and I hope you will be in good health and complete the tour safely. Thank you very much.
And so it goes, Mr. Chabatake. I love you, Riko Nakayama. Thank you very much.
I love you.
It's done. Emi-chan.
Maya-chan's singing, dancing, expressiveness, and all her performances have always cheered me up.
I know that your throat must have been in immeasurable pain after the abortion, but I was so impressed by the way you made it your own.
She recently gave birth and it was amazing! I haven't been able to go to the concerts, but I look forward to the day when I can go see you with my child!
I'll do my best! I will continue to support you!
Aww, good luck, and the same to you, sis! Good luck!
You know, moms can be, you know, moms, right?
You become a mother!
And at the same time, you become such a great mother that you forget what it's like to be a woman.
Take care of yourself from now on, Mi-chan. Enjoy your life with your children.
Please come to see me again.
It's a tough time for you.
Take care of yourself.
I'm in pain.
And next, Sakura-san.
I love you so much, Aya.
Thank you so much.
Thank you very much.
Is it okay if I start like this?
I'll only do it once in a while.
Oh, I get it.
Like when I get excited.
I love Hatsumi and Mirei's singing voice, not to mention their visuals, and their clothes are really cute.
I also refer to your shoes because they are all so fashionable. I'm waiting for more insta updates.
Thank you very much. Even the shoes are shown properly.
Shoes often get dirty, so I tend to use grail. Thank you very much.
Kayano-san, Po-chan big love!
Be well forever!
Big love!
Thank you.
Yes, I'm coming. Rua-san.
Thank you for your hard work! I wish you a great SSA performance, and that it will be filled with many smiles, and I'll be cheering for you very, very, very much. Rittan!
Thank you very much. And thank you very, very much.
Ukiizaru-san. Mayama-san's solo cons were very comfortable. Please release an album of cover songs someday. I'm eagerly waiting for it.
I want to! Please wait for me!
Next, Yupi-chan.
I love Aya-chan's private clothes. What is the key point this time?
This time it's denim on denim for the outfit.
It's very spring-like, and it's one of my favorite points.
Thank you very much.
Cute.
There it is again.
Thank you for everything. Reika-san.
Thank you very much. I'm looking forward to seeing you on the spring tour.
I'm doing Mork too. I want to do Molek with Mire-chan.
After we go to MORQ, why don't we go together? Hey, guys. What do you think?
This is really a course of unfulfilled dreams.
Can I join from the middle?
Let's do the fragile.
Thank you.
I've never heard of you before.
It's my first time.
I don't know... but neither do her fans.
I put it on TikTok, and I thought, "What's this?" and I skipped it, and when I went back...
And when I skipped back to it, it said it was Minerei-chan.
I don't know... Morita-san...
That Mororoku...
The World Championships.
Yes, he's a representative of Japan.
But you know, there's a condition that if you become the Japanese representative, you have to be able to go to the World Championships with mercy.
It costs a lot of money for airfare and so on.
So, Hime might be able to go, too, and become a representative of Japan.
Yes, but I'm going to give it my best shot.
Please do your best.
They laugh at me so much.
I'm sorry, it's because I'm a representative of Japan that I can't perform live.
I can't go to the live show because I'm a member of the Japan team.
Let's go to the live reschedule and cheer for everyone.Let's go live reschedule and support everyone.
Yes, what should we do?
Let's go cheer for 5 or 6.
What shall we do?
Yes, and then Ishii, Po-chan, thank you very much for everything.
Thank you very much.
I'm surprised at how beautiful you've become recently. I'll continue to support you, beautiful, cute and wild.
It's wild!
Hatsumi, I love your regular live performances as well as Mayama in variety shows.
Your voice is so easy to understand and I'm so proud of you.
I was at a reading performance the other day, and the pronunciation of the voice actors is really amazing.
That's why I want to master my voice even more.
Hatsumi, please continue to watch over me.
Next, let's go to Rikkku!
Rikkku-chan, are you up?
Is this Rika-chan? Is this Rika-chan or not Rika-chan?
Rika-chan or Rika-chan?
I love you more than anything in the world, both as an idol and as a human being.
The person I want to be most is Ayaka Yasumoto. Thank you very much.
You'll always be important to me. Thank you for everything.
I love you so much Thank you so much Now that I used to be bad at work
Durrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr.
Ah, Maharu, Yappi, Mirei, Yappi.
I am so glad that the spring tour will be held again this year. The spring tour is my first time going to Okinawa myself.
If you have any recommendations, I'd be glad to know where you recommend, Mirei-chan.
Thank you for everything, and let's raise your voice for the first time in 3 years.
Well, Okinawa, but if you go to Churaumi Aquarium for the first time, I think you will be very impressed.
There are big whale sharks and so on.
I also recommend going to the islands.
Please enjoy yourself.
I also want to try the Agu pork shabu shabu shabu.
Wow, there are so many things to eat.
Wow, I want to eat it now.
There are so many. I'm looking forward to it.
So, Ali, I'm always rooting for you.
I'm in love. I'm in love.
I'm in love.
Oh my god. I got a shot of Nakayama.
I got a shot of Nakayama.
Of course, I was on the fan's side.
That side? That side.
I said I fell in love with him, so I said I fell in love with him just now.
On Mr. Nakayama's side.
I'm not taking pictures of Mr. Nakayama's side.
I've always been on the fans' side.
I've always said so, even at live shows.
If you want.
I say it too.
You're uniting the fans, aren't you?
That's right.
Members of the Ebituf fan club.
But you're the best TO. But I don't know about later. But...
You don't know? You don't know? I only know the characteristic parts.
I don't know, but I've told you that I fell in love with him.
I'll continue. Mr. Takapi.
Thank you very much.
On a personal note, I recently celebrated my 30th birthday.
Happy birthday!
Even if the tenth place changes, I am happy to spend the same time with EBICHU,
I am happy to be able to spend the same time with Ebichu in this way.
And even if the 10th place of age changes in the future,
I hope we will be able to spend a healthy life together.
Let's stay healthy!
Let's go!
Mokkun-san.
I have been waiting for the EbituNet signing. It has been a long time since I attended a signing event in Fukuoka about 5 years ago.
March 9 is the graduation ceremony, but I'm hoping that I will be able to go home quickly after finishing other work and preparing for the next day's class, and watch the live streaming.
Even if I can't make it on that day, I'm looking forward to missing it and receiving the checkered photos from Fukuoka.
I am looking forward to the upcoming tour in April. Please take care of yourself and do your best.
I wonder if Mokkun-san is also a teacher?
I guess you are a teacher, aren't you?
I guess you are a teacher, right? I know it's a tough job, but please do your best.
Thank you for all your hard work.
Next
Miiko-san. I love you, Aya. I will continue to support you. Thank you very much.
Ms. Kawasaki. Thank you very much.
I am very much looking forward to the spring tour of the voice-out session.
Let's enjoy the space you have finally returned to.Enjoy the space you finally have back.
Let's enjoy it!
Oooh!
Thank you.
Next, Yukidaruma-san. Thank you very much.
I love the chirpy atmosphere of EBICHU and it always cheers me up. Please give us a word to cheer us up.
A word to cheer me up?
Eat and sleep!
That's not what I mean.
Eating and sleeping is the most energizing thing you can do.
I just told you to take a bath and go to bed.
I said go to bed and sleep.
You can't beat sleep, can you?
That's true.
I feel better.
Let's go. Miitan.
We are the Kahoriko generation who will start working from April. Looking forward to receiving this cheki. When I receive it, I will use it as a good luck charm and do my best at work.
Lastly, please give us a message of support that you heard in the Nakayama section.
Eiii! Yeah! Oh!
Goo! Goo outside! Oh!
It's so wiggly.
Go for it!
Don't hold on. We'll work together.
You're a stickler, aren't you? You can cheer her up.
Chico will do his best.
Let's do our best together.
Chico, I'll do my best.
Marin, I'm very happy about your first online signing.
I'm happy for you. It was my first time and I won.
Thank you, Marin.
Next, Kenta-san.
You always give me energy, excitement, and strength to overcome challenges.
I always receive energy, excitement, and a strong feeling to overcome challenges from you.
I also receive a gentle support for my sad and unfulfilled feelings.
I was watching the broadcast of the first performance of the song on time while I was still a junior high school student,
I couldn't stop crying because of the sadness of the Great East Japan Earthquake the year before, the successors, and the situation I was in at the time, so I watched it over and over again,
I have been a member of the family for more than 10 years now.
I will continue to support you.
Thank you very much.
It has been such a long time since it ended. Since then.
Thank you.
I'll go now.
Thank you, Akaruku, ah, thank you, Ujicha Panda.
I am always energized by the bright and lovely Mirei.
Please continue to challenge new things one after another and polish your potential, Mirei. I'll be rooting for you.
Thank you very much.
Polishing and polishing.
Migaki-migaki-migaki!
Thank you very much!
Thank you, Fuji-kun!
I love you, Kahoriko! I always support you!
Thank you!
Cherry!
Cherries!
Mr. Goriken!
Thank you for always updating us on social networking sites! I love Ayariko dating!
I'm going to attend the tour this year! Looking forward to seeing you in Tohoku!
I will keep supporting you! Thank you very much!
Yes, I support you, Shogo! Thank you!
Hmmm...then...Nabe-san!
Always cheerful from Ayakami-sama!
Isn't God the God?
God...
You must be the one with Murakami-sama.
I hope you will take good care of yourself and finish the tour safely. Thank you very much.
I'll be there!
Ah! No bees...
Oh! Bee... thank you!
Next, Grandpa!
It's... it's written...
I didn't say that, it's written!
What!
Again!
What? You didn't say it again?
Your name, grandpa.
Grandpa!
Hello, Po-chan!Hello Po-chan!
You have been busy since the beginning of this year with the public recording Staplerfest stage.
We enjoyed the important stage at Karolisch. Thank you very much. Now you are going to start your spring tour.
I'm only excited to be on the first tour in the middle of 10 eves and with a voice out. I can shout with Po-chan with all my might! Yay!
Well then, please take care of yourself as the season is changing.
Thank you!
The name is scary! It says my name is scary! It says in the comments that it's not a comedic swear word.
It says so. It's written right, right, right. It's a name.
Then I'll continue. Aika, I always support you. Thank you!
Grandpa is good.
I'm sorry, Grandpa.
I said it while pronouncing it.
I'm sorry for the comment.
I'm sure you're right.
You mean you're a grandpa?
Is he a real grandpa, or is he a grandpa, or is he a grandpa?
If you want, we can do it later.
Yeah, you could say that.
Yes, if you tell me. Thank you very much.
That's it. I'm thrilled.
Next, Hada-chan. I really love Rika-chan's singing voice.
The other day at karaoke, I sang Sunset Sunset and Happy End and Then and Then, and I got a high score of 83 .75.
Also, on a personal note, I cried and decided to go to a local hotel. I would like to ask for your congratulations, good luck and ganbatte mayama from Rika-chan.
I will be going to the spring tour in Hokkaido and will be waving a purple penda.
Isn't that the girl I don't understand? The girl who just said that. I don't know.
Maybe it was Hada-chan. I think it was.
Is it different? No? No? You are so kind. You wrote your comment like this. I'm very happy.
First of all, congrats on the hotel! From now on, hotels should prepare a lot of American keys.
What do you mean? Carabons.
I mean, you know, make sure they have plenty of candy bars. I know it's not easy for you.
I know it's tough on the sun, but we'll do our best!
I'm looking forward to seeing you on the Hull tour. Thank you very much.
Next, Shishimaru-kun.
In the opening movie at the FC event,
Aya-chan threw the pipe chair she was sitting on and lost her seat.
It is funny. Very pleasant.
I look forward to seeing more interesting Aya-chan in the future.
Thank you very much.
I didn't intend for it to be funny in any way,
It just came naturally.
I'll go next time.
Thank you, Tomomo-chan.
Mirei, I love you more than anything in the world.
I'm going to propose to Mirei now, so please say no.
Please say no.
Mirei, please marry me.
I want to propose directly to you when the face-to-face award meeting is restored.
I'm sorry. It's not a good time. I'm sorry. Thank you. I said no.
I'm the best genius in the world again today. Yay.
But I'm sorry. Let's get married again someday.
I was going to propose.
That's what I call a reverse marriage proposal. Someday again.
I can't do it by getting married. Next life.
You're right. Yes, that's for sure.
Next lifetime or so. The next life or so, please.
The next life? The next world? The next world?
The next world. Next, thank you very much, Itton-chan.
The important story was interesting. I would like to see a sequel to Machiko.
I want to do Machiko 2, and also, I met the members of Machiko for the first time in about 5 years the other day,
Oh, that's nice.
We had dinner together.
It was really nice.
I was so happy.
You were underage at that time, right?
That's right, that's right.
He told me I had become an adult.
I was told that I had become an adult.
That made me happy.
I will do my best. I'll try to do my best.
You don't look good at all.
I just spilled some water.
It's not showing at all.
There's one for each of us.
They'll know everything.
But you're okay? You kept your seat.
You're on your knees.
Your seat is secure.
I'm coming.
Black Cat. Let's go to Saitama Super Arena.
Let's go. Thank you very much.Let's go. Thank you very much.
And now the last one! This will be the last one.
Last one?
Last one!
Risako!
Ebichu has been supporting me every day!
And my guess, Rika-chan!
You are the color of my life!
Thank you for everything! I love you! I'm so happy!
I hope you have lots of fun and stay happy!
I'm looking forward to your spring tour in April. If you have any koho that you are thinking of using as a good-luck charm for the spring tour, please let me know secretly.
Well, this has been my good-luck charm cosmetics recently.
At that time, she gave everyone Hermes lip gloss and lip oil as a gift. Thank you, Kanako-chan.
Thank you, Kanako-chan. It has become a good luck charm, or an item that I definitely use when I have important work to do.
It's a little bit expensive, so it might be a little bit of a badge, but if you want, let's use it as a good luck charm together when you get it too, Rikako-chan. Thank you very much.
And the last one is Natsumi Akane. I am enjoying raising my child while listening to the songs of EBITCHU.
I am enjoying raising my child while playing the songs of EBITCHU.
I will continue to follow it. Thank you very much.
Please come to the concert with me next time. With your children, with your children, with your children.
With your children, with your children, with your children.
I'll be there next time.
Nana-chan, Mirei-chan, thank you for everything.
Nana-chan, thank you for everything.
This is the last one. Thank you.
Okay, Yukina-chan, next.
I love you, Ko-chan. I will always support you. Thank you very much.
Lastly, this person.
KANEGON. I'm looking forward to the spring tour.
I'd like to hear a blonde soon.
You don't have it, do you?
I want to be sealed.
That's for sure.
It's urgent, isn't it? Urgent, urgent, urgent.
Yes, it is. Yes, it is.
I might want to see it. I'd like to see it.
Really.
With this.
Okay, everyone.
For those whose names were called, thank you very much for watching.
For those who were not called, thank you very much for signing up.
It seems like there are more variations in the poses of the private suits, doesn't it? Yes, I think so.
I signed and dated all of them carefully, so please look forward to receiving them in the mail.
So, it's almost time for me to finish,
It all went by so fast.
It went by so fast.
It was fun even though I was not born.
Thank you very much.
It was fun. It's been a while. Wouldn't you like to do a webcast where you just talk?
What do you think? A Zadan-kai? Maybe a Zadan-kai.
But most of all, don't you want to meet everyone up close and personal? That's right.
Since we don't have any free shows. We want to have a benefit party. It would be nice to see the inside of everyone.
It would be super fun. I'd be happy if we have that kind of opportunity again.
I'd be happy to have such an opportunity again, and I'm sure we can hear everyone's voices live on the spring tour. I'm really looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to that.
I'll be more than happy to hear them in a one-man show,
I hope you will come to the spring tour. Please come to a venue near you.
Please come and visit us. Please do.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it. Thank you very much.
First of all, is that it? I'll see it in Odate.
Yes, on the 21st.
The sister who is always holding it down will be the last one, so please come on out and see her.
I hope you all will join me in seeing the last of the Canadenbuilders' sisters,
I hope that you will join me in bringing her last day to a close. Graduation.
Yes.
There will be a lot of events coming up,
I'll have more chances to see you all,
I'd like to have another benefit party like this,
I'd like to do it again.
Hey, hey, hey.
I wonder if there will be a face-to-face handshake this year?
I wonder.
I'll keep an eye on what's going on in the world.
It would be nice if we could. I really hope so.
I wonder. Maybe.
Hey, hey, hey.
From now on, too.
I mean, from now on, even from spring.
I have a lot to look forward to,
Next week, this weekend, I'll be signing autographs for my younger sisters online,Next week, this weekend, will be the online signing for my sisters,
If you are going to be there, please look forward to it.
Please come and join us. Thank you for your time today.
Thank you very much.
It was fun.
Well, I will see you again somewhere.
That's all for us,
SHISEI WISH WORLD.
Bye bye.
Thank you.
Good night.
Yay!
Do you expect any improvement in your future activities?
Do you anticipate any improvement in your future activities?
Do you anticipate any improvement in future activities?
Do you anticipate any improvements in future activities?